<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NKind - A model checker for Lustre</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NKind - A model checker for Lustre</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Document</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 20:55:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/</guid>
      <description>Document Requirement In order to run NKind, the following software are necessary to be installed in the system:
 Java 11 or later Z3  Usage NKind is used in command line environment by specifying the Lustre input.
1  nkind example.lus   Arguments list below can also be specified to control the operation:
 --max-round &amp;lt;INTEGER&amp;gt; set the max unroll length in BMC. --timeout &amp;lt;INTEGER&amp;gt; set the verification timeout, and UNKNOWN will be returned if timeout threshold is reached.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/download/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2022 15:15:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/download/</guid>
      <description>Download Version 1.0.0
Click here(md5|sha1) to get the latest version of NKind.
Click here(md5|sha1) to get examples for NKind.
License NKind is copyrighted 2021-2022 by East China Normal University, Shanghai, China. All rights reserved.
NKind is available for research and evaluation purposes only and can not be used in a commercial environment. NKind is provided as is, without warranties or conditions of any kind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 21:50:51 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/main/</guid>
      <description>Introduction NKind is an SMT-based infinite-state model checking tool, which is mainly used for proving or disproving properties of synchronous reactive system models written in Lustre.
NKind mainly relies on te powerful SMT-solver Z3 to validate or invalidate the properties. For properties that are proved to be invalid, a counterexample will be returned. Apart from the traditional verification for safety properties, NKind supports liveness properties as well, bridging the gap in liveness property checking in Lustre.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
